Speaker 1: She can’t close the car boot because there are
She can’t close the car boot because there are too many suitcases.
Speaker 2: He can’t reach the laptop because he isn’t
He can’t reach the laptop because he isn’t tall enough.
Speaker 1: The sofa doesn’t fit because it’s
The sofa doesn’t fit because it’s too long.
Speaker 2: She can’t pay the bill because she doesn’t have
She can’t pay the bill because she doesn’t have enough money.
Speaker 1: She has problems sleeping because she drinks
She has problems sleeping because she drinks too much coffee.
Speaker 2: She didn’t want to swim because the water wasn’t
She didn’t want to swim because the water wasn’t warm enough.
Speaker 1: She didn’t buy the sunglasses because they were
She didn’t buy the sunglasses because they were too expensive.
Speaker 2: He couldn’t make the cake because he didn’t have
He couldn’t make the cake because he didn’t have enough eggs.
Speaker 1: They didn’t like the beach because there were
They didn’t like the beach because there were too many people.